Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 3: Boxes 45-66
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 3: Boxes 45-66
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 3: Boxes 45-66
5583/3
Kheel Center
86.3 linear ft.
Records, publications.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Publications, manuals, policies, and plans issued by a large sample of Fortune 500 corporations and by a variety of organizations, such as professional and trade associations, government agencies, and educational and cultural organizations. The materials issued by corporations include company histories, employee newsletters, employee benefit plans, personnel practice manuals, performance appraisal forms, affirmative action policies, training brochures, job descriptions, and career development programs as well as national trade association documents and recruitment material.
Several economic activities(sectors) are represented in the collection, such as manufacturing, transportation, mining, banking, insurance, utilities, trade, and services. Corporations whose pamphlets are held in the collection include AT&T, Bethlehem Steel, Bell Telephone System, Firestone Tire & Rubber, Ford Motor Co., General Electric, General Foods, General Mills, General Motors, Goodyear Tire & Rubber, Heinz, International Harvester, Johnson & Johnson, Lockheed Aircraft Co., Maytag Co., Metropolitan Life Insurance Co., National Association of Manufacturers, Pennsylvania Railroad Co., Radio Corporation of America (RCA), Standard Oil, Tennessee Valley Authority, Union Carbide, and Westinghouse Electric among numerous other corporations.
Due to the volume of material in this collection the finding aid has been divided into four sections.
Section 1: Boxes 1-22
Section 2: Boxes 23-44
Section 3: Boxes 45-66
Section 4: Boxes 67-88
Boxes 82-87 have not been inventoried at this time.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Pullman Company.; Pullman-Standard Car Manufacturing Company.; Purdue University.; Quaker Oats Company.; Radio Corporation of America. RCA Victor Division.; Railway Express Agency.; Ralston Purina Company.; Republic Aviation Corporation.; Republic Steel Corporation.; Research Council for Economic Security.; Research Institute of America, inc.; Resistoflex Corporation.; Revere Copper and Brass Incorporated.; Reynolds Metals Company.; Reynolds Metals Company. Consumer Products Division.; R.J. Reynolds Tobacco Company.; Rheem Manufacturing Company.; Ritter-Conley Manufacturing.; Ritter Company.; Ritter-Pfaudler Corporation.; Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific Railway Company.; Rockbestos Product Corporation.; Royal McBee Corporation.; Rubber Manufacturers Association (U.S.); Rutgers University. Institute of Management and Labor Relations.; Rutgers University.; St. Regis Paper Company.; Samsonite Corporation.; San Diego Gas and Electric Company.; San Francisco Employers Council.; Sangamo Electric Company.; Sargent and Company (New Haven, Conn.); Scott Paper Company.; Sealed Power Corporation.; Sears, Roebuck and Company.; Shell Oil Company.; Sinclair Oil Corporation.; SKF Industries, inc.; Society for Advancement of Management.; Society of Federal Labor Relations Professionals (U.S.); Socony Mobil Oil Company.; Socony-Vacuum Oil Company.; Solar Aircraft Company.; Southern California Edison Company.; Southern New England Telephone Company.; Southern Pacific Company.; Southern Regional Council.; Spencer Kellogg and Sons, Inc.; Sperry Gyroscope Company, inc.; Sperry Rand Corporation.; Standard Oil Company.; Standard Oil Company of California.; Standard Oil Company (Indiana); Standard Oil Company of New Jersey; Standard Oil Company (Ohio); Standard Oil Development Company.; State Farm Insurance Companies.; State Farm Mutual Automobile Insurance Company.; State Mutual Life Assurance Company (Worcester, Mass.); John B. Stetson Hat Company.; Stromberg-Carlson Telephone Manufacturing Co.; Studebaker Corporation.610:; Studebaker-Packard Corporation.; Sun Oil Company.; Supermarket Institute.; Swift & Company (Chicago, IL); Sylvania Electric Products, Inc.; Sylvania Electronics Systems.; Taylor Instrument Companies.; Tennessee Valley Authority.; Texaco, inc.; Texas Company.; Texas Instruments Incorporated.; Thatcher Glass Manufacturing Company.; Thompson Products, inc.; Thompson Ramo Wooldridge, inc.; Time, inc.; Time Share Corporation.; Timken Company.; Todd Shipyards Corporation.; Toledo Labor-Management-Citizens Committee.; Transportation Association of America.; Travelers Insurance Companies.; TRW Inc.; Tennessee Valley Authority.; Twentieth Century Fund.; Twin City Rapid Transit Company.; Union Bag-Camp Paper Corporation.; Union Carbide Corporation.; Union Electric Company of Missouri.; Union Labor Life Insurance Company.; Union Oil Company of California.; Union Pacific Railroad Company.; Uniroyal, inc.; United Aircraft Corporation.; United Airlines.; United Brands Company.; United Gas Corporation.; United Shoe Machinery Corporation.; U.S. Atomic Energy Commission.; United States. Bureau of Employment Security.; United States. Bureau of Federal Credit Unions.; United States. Bureau of Labor-Management Reports.; United States. Bureau of Labor Standards.; United States Civil Service Commission.; United States. Civil Aeronautics Administration; United States. Congress.; Job Corps (U.S.); U.S. Congress of Mayors.; United States. Department of Agriculture.; United States. Department of Commerce.; United States. Department of Defense.; United States. Department of Health, Education, and Welfare.; United States. Department of Labor.; United States. Department of State.; United States. Department of the Air Force.; United States. Department of the Army.; United States. Department of the Interior.; United States. Department of the Navy.; United States. Department of the Treasury.; United States. Federal Trade Commission.; United States.General Accounting Office.; United States. General Services Administration.; United States. Internal Revenue Service.; United States. Interstate Commerce Commission.; Library of Congress; United States. National Labor Board.; United States.Office of Economic Opportunity.; United States. Railroad Retirement Board.; United States Rubber Company.; United States. Securities and Exchange Commission.; United States. Small Business Administration.; United States. Social Security Administration.; United States. Social Security Board.; United States Steel Corporation.; United States.Veterans Administration.; Volunteers in Service to America.; University of San Francisco.; Upjohn Company.; W.E. Upjohn Institute for Employment Research.; Upjohn Institute for Community Research.; Workmen's Compensation Board of Vancouver (B.C.); Victor Adding Machine Co.; University of Washington.; Washington University (Saint Louis, Mo.); Wayne State University.; Weirton Steel Corporation.; Welch's; University of the West Indies; West Virginia Pulp and Paper Company.; Western Electric Company.; Western Michigan University; Western Railways.; Western Union Telegraph Company.; Westinghouse Electric & Manufacturing Company.; Weston Electrical Company.; Weyerhaeuser Timber Company.; George Wiedemann Brewing Company.; H.W. Wilson Company; Wisconsin Electric Power Company; University of Wisconsin.; Wyandotte Chemicals Corporation.; Xerox Corporation.; Yale Towne Manufacturing Company; Yale University; Youngstown Sheet and Tube Company.; Zenith Radio Corporation.
Subjects:
Adult education; Aeronautics; Agricultural industries; Aluminum industry and trade; Airlines; Aircraft industry; Agricultural machinery; Architectural metal-work; Automobile industry and trade; Arbitration, Industrial; Agricultural chemicals industry; Audio equipment industry; Bituminous materials industry; Building trades; Buildings -- Environmental engineering; Banks and banking; Breweries; Baked products industry; Business consultants; Clothing trade; Coal mines and mining; Chemical industry; Compressor industry; Clerks (Retail trade); Computer industry; Cereal products; Consumer protection; Container industry; Credit unions; Clay industries; Cement industries; Copper alloys; Dairy products industry; Detergent industry; Executives --Training of; Electric power transmission; Electronics industries; Food industry and trade; Frozen foods and industry; Footwear industry; Fruit trade; Farm produce --Marketing -- Government policy; Finance, Public; Glass container industry; Glass manufacture; Gas extraction; Grain trade; Grocery trade; Gasket industry; Human capital; Hydroelectric power plants; Life insurance.; Iron industry and trade; Property insurance.; Casualty insurance.; Instructional materials industry; Health insurance.; Investment banking; Infant formula industry; Knit good industry; Labor unions; Local transit; Luggage industry; Logging; Medical supplies industry; Medicaid; Motor vehicle industry; Metal trade; Meat industry and trade; Military vehicle industry; Medical instruments and apparatus industry; Management; Measuring instruments; Natural gas pipelines; Notions (Merchandise); Newspaper publishing; Navigation equipment industry; National security; Office management; Office equipment and supplies; Petroleum refineries; Photographic industry; Paper folding (Graphic design); Public utilities; Paper products industry; Political participation; Plastics industry and trade; Pharmaceutical industry; Paint industry and trade; Public administration; Public opinion polls; Paper bag industry; Retail trade; Rug and carpet industry; Railroads; Rubber industry and trade; Railroad equipment industry; Roller bearings; Security systems industry; Service industries; Shipment of goods; Sanitary supply industry; Soybean industry; Slaughtering and slaughter-houses; Telecommunication.; Transportation equipment industry.; Trucking industry.; Trucks -- Design and construction.; Textile industry.; Trade associations.; Tobacco industry.; Universities and colleges.; Vocational education.; Wood products.; Welding equipment industry.; Woolen goods industry.
Form and Genre Terms:
Records.; Publications
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
RELATED MATERIALS
Other sections of this Collection:
5583/3: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3 5583/3: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 1: Boxes 1-22
5583/3: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 2: Boxes 23-44
5583/3: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 4: Boxes 67-88
Boxes 82-87 have not been inventoried at this point.
Related Collections:
5880: Archives Organization File V, Additional Company Documents
5583/1: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1
5583/2: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
5583/4: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 4. Corporate and Organizational Publications
5583/5: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 5
5583/6: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 6
5956: Archives Organization File Additional records
CONTAINER LIST
- Box: 45, Folder: 1 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Disability Benefit Plan, 1950; Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
    Language: English.
  - Item 2: Our Group Insurance Plan, 1954; Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: National Hospital Association Medical, Hospital and Surgical Plan for Family Groups, Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Accident Prevention Manual, 1953; Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Request for Prescription Safety Glasses, Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
- Box: 45, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Stewards Training & Recreation, Inc., Publication (Box 45, Folder 2)
- Box: 45, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Personnel Services, 1968; Publication (Box 45, Folder 3)
- Box: 45, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Service Training Program, Publication (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: A Brief on the Educational Department's principal Functional Activities, Publication (Box 45, Folder 4)
- Box: 45, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Employee Development Program, Publication (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Expanded Training Report, 1960; Publication (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Training in the Panama Canal Company Canal Zone Government, 1957; Publication (Box 45, Folder 5)
- Box: 45, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Pan American World Airways, Inc. Cooperative Retirement Income Trust Plan for Pilots, 1967; Publication (Box 45, Folder 6)
- Box: 45, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Safety Organization, Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
- Box: 45, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: The Parker Plan, Publication (Box 45, Folder 8)
- Box: 45, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: PV Bugle, 1963; Publication (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: PV Bugle, 1964; Publication (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: PV Bugle, 1964; Publication (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: Employees of Peavey Company, 1964; Publication (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: PV Bugle, 1964; Publication (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: PV Bugle, 1964; Publication (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Item 7: PV Bugle, 1964; Publication (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Item 8: PV Bugle, 1964; Publication (Box 45, Folder 9)
- Box: 45, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Ninth Annual Joint Labor and Management Safety Conference, 1955; Publication (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: 9th Annual Joint Labor Management Safety Conference, Publication (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: 9th Annual Joint Labor & Management Safety Conference, 1955; Publication (Box 45, Folder 10)
- Box: 45, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Injury Frequency Report of 45 Member Mills, 1957; Publication (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: Injury Frequency Report of 44 Member Mills, 1958; Publication (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: Injury Frequency Report of 46 Member Mills, 1959; Publication (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: Injury Frequency Report of 44 Member Mills, 1960; Publication (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Item 5: Injury Frequency Report of 48 Member Mills, 1962; Publication (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Item 6: Injury Frequency Report of 47 Member Mills, 1961; Publication (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Item 7: Injury Frequency Report of 37 Member Mills, 1954; Publication (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Item 8: Injury Frequency Report of 39 Member Mills, 1955; Publication (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Item 9: Injury Frequency Report of 43 Member Mills, 1956; Publication (Box 45, Folder 11)
- Box: 45, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Test - Lesson 1, Publication (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: Test - Lesson 3, Publication (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: Lesson 2 - Test A, Publication (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Item 4: Lesson 4 - Test, Publication (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Item 5: Test - Lesson 5, Publication (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Item 6: Test - Lesson 6, Publication (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Item 7: Test - Lesson 7, Publication (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Item 8: Test - Lesson 8, Publication (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Item 9: Lesson 9 - Test, Publication (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Item 10: Test - Lesson 10, Publication (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Item 11: Test - Lesson 12, Publication (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Item 12: Test - Lesson 13, Publication (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Item 13: Test - Lesson 14, Publication (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Item 14: Test - Lesson 15, Publication (Box 45, Folder 13)
- Box: 45, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Training Program: Freight Rates Test Answer Sheets, 1970; Publication (Box 45, Folder 14)
- Box: 45, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Percenting: Test 1 Lesson 1 Part 1, Publication (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: Percenting: Test Lesson 1 Part 2, Publication (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: Percenting: Test Lesson 2, Publication (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Item 4: Percenting: Test Lesson 3, Publication (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Item 5: Percenting: Test Lesson 4, Publication (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Item 6: Percenting: Test Lesson 5, Publication (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Item 7: Divisions: Test Lesson 6, Publication (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Item 8: Divisions: Test Lesson 7, Publication (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Item 9: Divisions: Test Lesson 8, Publication (Box 45, Folder 15)
- Box: 45, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Training Program: Freight Divisions Test Answers, Publication (Box 45, Folder 16)
- Box: 45, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Instructor's Manual, 1970; Publication (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Item 2: Training Program: Freight Divisions, Publication (Box 45, Folder 17)
- Box: 45, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Training Program: Freight Divisions, Publication (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: Training Program: Freight Divisions, Publication (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Item 3: Training Program: Freight Divisions, Publication (Box 45, Folder 18)
- Box: 45, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Training Program: Freight Divisions, Publication (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Item 2: Training Program: Freight Divisions, Publication (Box 45, Folder 19)
- Box: 45, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Training Program: Freight Divisions, Publication (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Item 2: Training Program: Freight Rates, Publication (Box 45, Folder 20)
- Box: 45, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Training Program: Freight Rates, Publication (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Item 2: Training Program: Freight Rates, Publication (Box 45, Folder 21)
- Box: 45, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Training Program: Freight Rates, Publication (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Item 2: Training Program: Freight Rates, Publication (Box 45, Folder 22)
- Box: 45, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Training Program: Freight Rates, Publication (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - Item 2: Training Program: Freight Rates, Publication (Box 45, Folder 23)
- Box: 45, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Training Program: Freight Rates, Publication (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - Item 2: Training Program: Freight Rates, Publication (Box 45, Folder 24)
- Box: 45, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 45, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Training Program: Freight Rates, Publication (Box 45, Folder 25)
  - Item 2: Training Program: Freight Rates, Publication (Box 45, Folder 25)
  - Item 3: Training Program: Freight Rates, Publication (Box 45, Folder 25)
- Box: 45, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 45, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Instructions for Supervisors in Connection with the Handling of Discipline, 1971; Publication (Box 45, Folder 26)
  - Item 2: Safety Rules, 1968; Publication (Box 45, Folder 26)
  - Item 3: Instructor's Manual, Publication (Box 45, Folder 26)
- Box: 45, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Improvements in Your Medical Care Plan, 1972; Publication (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - Item 2: Medical Care Plan, Publication (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - Item 3: Summary of Medical Care Plan, Publication (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - Item 4: Group Life Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - Item 5: Employment Policy, Publication (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - Item 6: Military Service Policy, Publication (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - Item 7: Leave of Absence Policy, Publication (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - Item 8: Sickness and Disability Policy, Publication (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - Item 9: Program fir Improving Cooperation and Communication Between Management and Its Employees, Publication (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - Item 10: Vacation Policy, Publication (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - Item 11: Holiday Policy, Publication (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - Item 12: Guide for Payment or Reimbursement of Relocation Expenses Incurred by Non-Agreement Employees Transferred in Connection with the Merger of the Pennsylvania Railroad and the New York Central Railroad, 1968; Publication (Box 45, Folder 27)
- Box: 45, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Headlight on Passenger Sales & Services, 1956; Publication (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - Item 2: Headlight on Passenger Sales & Services, 1957; Publication (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - Item 3: Headlight on Passenger Sales & Services, 1957; Publication (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - Item 4: Headlight on Passenger Sales & Services, 1957; Publication (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - Item 5: Headlight on Passenger Sales & Services, 1957; Publication (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - Item 6: Welcome Aboard the Broadway Limited, 1957; Publication (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - Item 7: Headlight on Passenger Sales & Services, 1957; Publication (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - Item 8: Headlight on Passenger Sales & Services, 1957; Publication (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - Item 9: Headlight on Passenger Sales & Services, 1957; Publication (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - Item 10: Headlight on Passenger Sales & Services, 1957; Publication (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - Item 11: Headlight on Passenger Sales & Services, 1957; Publication (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - Item 12: Headlight on Passenger Sales & Services, 1958; Publication (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - Item 13: Headlight on Passenger Sales & Services, 1959; Publication (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - Item 14: Headlight on Passenger Sales & Services, 1959; Publication (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - Item 15: Transportation Apprentice Training Course, 1954; Publication (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - Item 16: Personnel Apprentice Program, 1958; Publication (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - Item 17: Confidential Supervisory Personnel Appraisal Program of the Pennsylvania Railroad, 1958; Publication (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - Item 18: The Personnel Manager, 1959-1962 (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - Item 19: Pittsburgh Region Report, 1962; Publication (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - Item 20: Headlight on Passenger Sales & Services, 1958; Publication (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - Item 21: Headlight on Passenger Sales & Services, 1958; Publication (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - Item 22: Headlight on Passenger Sales & Services, 1958; Publication (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - Item 23: Headlight on Passenger Sales & Services, 1957; Publication (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - Item 24: Headlight on Passenger Sales & Services, 1958; Publication (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - Item 25: Headlight on Passenger Sales & Services, 1958; Publication (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - Item 26: Headlight on Passenger Sales & Services, 1958; Publication (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - Item 27: Headlight on Passenger Sales & Services, 1958; Publication (Box 45, Folder 28)
- Box: 46, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Sooner Or Later, Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: A Outline of the Penco Pension Trust Plan for Financial Institutions, 1952; Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Early Retirement and Survivor's Benefit Options, 1955; Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Box: 46, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Fun for You and Your Family, 1963; Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Box: 46, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Pennsylvania State University Policy Manual, 1965-1968 (Box 46, Folder 3)
- Box: 46, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Conference on a University-Union Education Program, 1955; Publication (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: The Annual Community Service Institute, 1955; Publication (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Labor Education Service, 1955; Publication (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Labor Education Service: Cuban Medical Workers Institute, 1955; Publication (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Evaluation of Foreign Labor Team Programs, 1954-1955 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Summary Proceedings for the Sixth Annual PFL Institute of The Pennsylvania Federation of Labor, 1955; Publication (Box 46, Folder 4)